

Sara Abbasi
UI/UX Designer

Date of birth: 1995

Location: Bussum, Netherlands

Email: sara2196a@gmail.com

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/saraabasi

Portfolio: https://sarahbio.github.io/portfolio/

Website: https://sarahbio.github.io/portfolio/

Hi! I'm Sara, a UI/UX designer based in Netherlands and graduated with a BE of computer engineering(IT). I've dedicated two years of my career to working as a UI/UX designer at Paramount Students Company. I create modern and easy-to-use website and mobile designs. I mainly work in Figma. Feel free to message me, the quickest way to reach out to me is via an email.

\*\*I'm currently seeking new opportunities for remote employment or freelance projects.\*\*

# **Employment Experience**

May 2023 - Present (+3 mos)
Product Designer at Paramount Students

Full time - Remote - London, England

**December 2021 - May 2023** (1 yr 6 mos)

UI/UX Designer at Paramount Students

Full time - Remote - Istanbul, Turkey

### Languages

Persian

English

Turkish

### **Education**

2014 - 2019 - Payam Noor University

Bachelor of Computer Engineering (IT) - Iran

#### Soft skills

- Communication
- Time management
- Teamwork
- Creativity
- Attention to details
- Desire to learn
- Meeting deadlines

# **Specilizing**

### UI/UX

- Landing Page
- User Flow
- Wireframing
- Logo Design
- Prototyping
- Mockups
- Site Map

#### **Technical Skills**

**Figma** 

Photoshop

Web Design (HTML/CSS)

Bootstrap